Finding Aid for University of Michigan News and Information Services Photographs, 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Series G 1949-1970 (Mainly Aerial Negatives)
  - Miscellaneous 5" x 7" Aerial Negatives
    - Clinton Engineering 1959 (Box G3)
    - Dearborn (downtown) 1958 (Box G3)
    - Dundee Cement Plant undated, 2 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Hawthorne Hills 1949, 2 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Hoover Plant 1959 (Box G3)
    - Hospital Complex 1969 (Box G3)
    - Killen Gravel Company 1959 (Box G3)
    - Milan Subdivision 1959 (Box G3)
    - Markley and Hospital undated (Box G3)
    - Mott Hospital (architects rendering, non-aerial) undated (Box G3)
    - North Campus (from the East) 1969 (Box G3)
    - North Campus Housing undated (Box G3)
    - Northwood Construction Period (North Campus views) undated (Box G3)
    - Northwood I and II Apartment Area 1969 (Box G3)
    - O & S Bearing (Whitmore Lake) 1960, 2 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Observatory (Peach Mountain) 1960 (Box G3)
    - Observatory 1970, 4 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Porsath Farm undated (Box G3)
    - Radio Telescope 1970, 3 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Road Commission Yard 1950 (Box G3)
    - Reynolds Chemical 1960 (Box G3)
    - Stadium and Events Building (with new turf; empty) 1969 (Box G3)
    - Stadium (U-M) undated, 3 envelopes (Box G3)
    - Steere Pumping Station 1951 (Box G3)
    - Strawberry Lake 1950 (Box G3)
    - Trailer Park (West of Ann Arbor 1959 (Box G3)
    - Trailer Park (Herman Schmidt) 1960 (Box G3)
    - University Hospital undated (Box G3)
    - Varsity Press Club 1992 (Box G3)
    - Weber's (non-aerial) 1951 (Box G3)
    - Whitmore Lake Trailer Park 1960 (Box G3)
    - Wick's Lumber Company 1959 (Box G3)
    - Willow Run
      - East 1957 (Box G3)
      - Final Approach (from inside plane) 1957 (Box G3)
      - Northeast 1957 (Box G3)
      - Southeast 1957 (Box G3)
    - Wiltsie Farm and Airport 1950 (Box G3)
- Series H circa 1949-1975 (Various Sized Negatives and Color Transparencies) circa 1949-1975
  SERIES H (2 linear ft.; ca. 1949-1975) includes various sized black and white negatives (mainly 7" x 7" and 8" x 10"), color negatives (8" x 10" and 2 1/4" x 2 1/4") and a folder of slides.
  The negatives in Series H represent a variety of campus scenes and activities, arranged numerically in chronological order. The images are mainly of buildings, drawings, models, maps, athletics and aerial shots. Included are six color negatives in a separate numerical arrangement.
  The February 1992 accession in box H1 is comprised of slides of Michigras and sports (chiefly basketball) from 1960 to 1969.
  The color transparencies in box H2 date from 1951 through 1975. Most are 4" x 5" in size. Subjects include athletics, marching bands, campus buildings, the Ford Nuclear Reactor, and commencement.
  - O Series 0-1--0-138 1949-1968 (and earlier "historical") negatives identified on envelopes (Box H1)
  - OC1-OC6 (color negatives) 1955-1960
    - OC-1 Students Walking in Front of Alumni Memorial Hall, and Crossing State Street toward Michigan Union September 1955 (Box H1)
    - OC-2 Band in Company Front in Empty Stadium September 1957 (Box H1)
    - OC-3 Marching Band, Massed Bands-Band Day October 1960 (Box H1)
    - OC-4 Football Cheerleaders, William D. Revelli, George R. Cavender, Marching Band October 15, 1955 (Box H1)
    - OC-5 Massed Bands on Field, Band Day 1955 (Box H1)
    - OC-6 Band Day (188 High School bands massed on field) 1957 (Box H1)
  - Slides 1960-1969
    - Michigras 1960-1964 (Box H1)
    - Athletics
      - Baseball Team 1966 (Box H1)
      - Basketball
        - Cazzie Russell and Coach Strack 1966 (Box H1)
        - Basketball vs. Kentucky 1967 (Box H1)
      - Canham, Don (Box H1)
      - Football Practice 1967 (Box H1)
      - Hockey Team, 1966-67 1969 (Box H1)
      - Michigamua (Box H1)
      - Sailing Club (Box H1)
  - Negatives University of Michigan Football Team 1960s
    - Group Shot 1962 Squad (color) (C-62) (Box H1)
    - Team Pictures 1964 (color) (C-71) (Box H1)
    - Team Shots 1968 (color) (C85) (Box H1)
    - Press Day, Football Team 1968 (C-106) (Box H1)
  - Color Transparencies Series (C-1--C-122) (Box H2)
    - C-3 Law Quadrangle Dining Hall, Exterior 1951 (Box H2)
    - C-3 School of Public Health Carbon Monoxide Research (Lab technician at Detroit Receiving Hospital) 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-4 Engineering Research Institute Upper Atmosphere Research, Aeronautical Engineering 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-5 Michifish (Student Activities) 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-6 Museum of Archaeology Division of the Orient, Costume and Artifacts 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-6 Football, Action Shots, Michigan vs. Northwestern 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-7 Exhibit Museum, Dioramas and Displays 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-8 Football Stadium, Block M 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-9 Michigras Carnival (Student Activities) 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-9 Football Stadium, Stands 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-10 Women's Swimming Pool, Exterior 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-11 President's House, Exterior 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-11 Football, Action Shots, Michigan vs. Iowa 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-12 Student Activities Building, Exterior 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-12 Clements Library, Exterior 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-13 West Engineering, Exterior 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-13 Student Activities Building, Interiors 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-14 University Hospital, Alice Crocker Lloyd Radiation Center, Cesium Theratron 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-16 Phoenix Memorial Project, Ford Nuclear Reactor 1958 (Box H2)
    - C-16 Homecoming Displays, Michigan vs. Penn. 1954 (Box H2)
    - C-17 U-M Research Institute, Willow Run Laboratories, Project Michigan 1958 (Box H2)
    - C-17 Alumni Memorial Hall, Exterior 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-18 Football, Action Shots, Michigan vs. Iowa 1958 (Box H2)
    - C-18 Angell Hall, Exterior 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-19 Angell Hall, Exterior 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-19 Football, Michigan vs. Minnesota 1958 (Box H2)
    - C-20 Exhibit Museum, Dioramas 1958 (Box H2)
    - C-21 Men's Glee Club, Dr. Duey Conducting 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-22 Harlan Hatcher, Portrait 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-22 Drum Major and Girl with Brown Jug 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-23 Commencement, Color Guard with New U-M Flag 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-23 Drum Major 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-24 Undergraduate Library, Exterior at Night 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-25 Football, Michigan vs. Michigan State 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-26 Football, Michigan vs. Oregon State 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-27 Commencement, Graduates and Flags 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-27 Athletic Administration Building, Exterior 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-28 Commencement Speaker, Sir Geoffery Crowther 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-28 Stellfeld Library of Musicology, Close-up of open book 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-29 Commencement, Harlan Hatcher 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-29 Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, Radiation Caves 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-31 Commencement, Procession 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-31 Phoenix Memorial Laboratory and Ford Nuclear Reactor 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-32 Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, Ford Nuclear Reactor, and Cooley Building 1955 (Box H2)
    - C-32 Commencement 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-33 Graduation 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-34 Aeronautical Engineering Laboratory, Wind Tunnel Construction 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-34 Graduation Caps and Tassels 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-35 Aeronautical Engineering Laboratory, Air Tanks 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-35 Willow Run, Runways 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-36 Willow Run, Airport and Runways 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-36 Aeronautical Engineering Laboratory, Air Storage Tanks 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-37 Automotive Engineering Building, Early Construction 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-37 Marching Band, Louis Elbell Directing 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-38 School of Architecture and Design, Unistrut Building, Exterior at Night 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-38 Homecoming Displays 1957 (Box H2)
    - C-39 North Hall, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-39 Michigras Floats 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-40 Burton Tower and Diag 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-40 Kresge Library, Interior 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-41 Angell Hall, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-42 Kellogg Institute, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-42 Band Day, Massed High School Bands and Marching Band, Northwestern Game 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-43 East Medical School, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-43 Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, Ford Nuclear Reactor, Automotive Engineering Laboratory, and Cooley Building 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-43 Museum of Natural History, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-44 Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, Exterior 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-44 Health Service Building, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-45 Barbour Gymnasium, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-45 Automotive Engineering Laboratory, exterior 1956 (Box H2)
    - C-46 East Medical Building, Exterior 1960 (Box H2)
    - C-47 Band Day, Massed High School Bands and Marching Band 1959 (Box H2)
    - C-48 Mental Health Research Institute, Prof. Ralph Gerard 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-49 Mary Markley Building, Exterior (Box H2)
    - C-50 Medical Center, Exterior 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-52 Drum Major Bill McCann, for Vanguard record cover 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-53 Magneto-Fluid Dynamics Laboratory, Lightning Maker 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-54 Phoenix Memorial Project, Ford Nuclear Reactor 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-55 Commencement, Mid-Year 1962 (Box H2)
    - C-56 Marching Band in Formation 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-57 Football, Action shot, Michigan vs. Michigan State 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-58 Michigras Floats 1958 (Box H2)
    - C-59 Harlan Hatcher at Home with Family 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-60 Marching Band 1961 (Box H2)
    - C-61 Exhibit Museum, Dioramas (Box H2)
    - C-63 Exhibit Museum, Dioramas (Box H2)
    - C-64 Drum Major Bill McCann 1963 (Box H2)
    - C-65 Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, Bulbous Bow, Prof. Richard Couch 1964 (Box H2)
    - C-66 Music School Building, Exterior 1964 (Box H2)
    - C-69 Mott Children's Hospital, Photo of Rendering 1964 (Box H2)
    - C-70 Football Coaches 1964 (Box H2)
    - C-73 North University Street, Natural Resources Building 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-74 Law Library, Check-out Desk 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-75 Law Quad, Hallway 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-76 Law Library, Interior 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-77 Administration Building, Exterior 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-78 Mason-Haven Hall, "the Fishbowl," 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-79 Law Quad, Archway 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-80 Law Quad, Hutchins Hall, Exterior 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-80 Baseball team 1968 (Box H2)
    - C-81 Football Team, Stadium (Box H2)
    - C-81 Marching Band 1964 (Box H2)
    - C-82 Holography, Lensless Photography 1968 (Box H2)
    - C-82 Undergraduate Library, Exterior 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-83 Robben Flemming, Donald Canham, Ronald Johnson, in Stadium 1968 (Box H2)
    - C-84 Rose Bowl Game, Pom-Poms 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-84 University of Michigan Flag 1968 (Box H2)
    - C-85 Law Quad, Frank and Becky Hill 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-86 Astronauts at Convocation 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-87 Rose Bowl Game 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-88 Rose Bowl Queen and Court 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-89 Rose Bowl Marching Band 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-90 Rose Bowl Fans 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-91 Drum Majors, some with Revelli 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-92 Basketball, Cassie Russell and Dave Strack 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-92 Marching Band, Cheerleaders, and Injured Football Players 1965 (Box H2)
    - C-93 Regents Flag 1971 (Box H2)
    - C-94 Events Building, Construction 1966 (Box H2)
    - C-95 Football Team Photos 1967 (Box H2)
    - C-96 Basketball, Team Photos 1967 (Box H2)
    - C-97 Basketball, Team Photos 1967 (Box H2)
    - C-99 Football, Freshman Team Photos 1967 (Box H2)
    - C-100 Hockey, Team Photos 1968 (Box H2)
    - C-105 Football Coaches and Band (Box H2)
    - C-108 Mechanical Engineering Classroom, Dave Cole 1968 (Box H2)
    - C-108 Dave Cole (Box H2)
    - Copy negs Baseball, Team Photos 1969 (Box H2)
    - C-109 Wolverine (taxidermy) 1969 (Box H2)
    - C-110 Exhibit Museum 1969 (Box H2)
    - C-110 Michigan Historical Collections, Proposed New Site 1971 (Box H2)
    - C-111 Power Center, Exterior 1973 (Box H2)
    - C-112 Rocket Launching Site, Kewenaw Peninsula 1972 (Box H2)
    - C-113 Administration Building, LS&A Building, and Student Activities Buildings, Exterior in Snow 1974 (Box H2)
    - C-114 Stearns Building and Collection 1975 (Box H2)
    - C-115 Wrestling Team 1975 (Box H2)
    - C-116 Power Center, Exterior 1975 (Box H2)
    - C-117 Campus Scenes, People Walking 1975 (Box H2)
    - C-118 Baseball Team 1975 (Box H2)
    - C-120 Track Team 1976 (Box H2)
    - C-121 Baseball Team 1976 (Box H2)
    - C-122 Angell Hall, Exterior 1976 (Box H2)
- Series I circa 1948-1998 (Various Sized Negatives, Prints, Slides (chiefly 35 mm)
  Series I (2.5 linear ft.; c. [1890s], 1950-1960, 1970-1998) consists of negatives of various sizes (chiefly 35 mm), some contact sheets and prints of various sizes, both color and black and white.
  The series is arranged by subject. Negatives include buildings, commencements, athletics, portraits, scenes and events. Prints in this series include images of sports teams, campus buildings, scenes, and events, students, student music groups, miscellaneous images from academic departments, and faculty and staff.
  - Aerial Photographs (negatives) (Box I-1)
    - Ann Arbor (Box I-1)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box I-1)
    - Campus (Box I-1)
    - North Campus (Box I-1)
  - Aerial Photographs (prints and slides) (Box I-1)
    (see also oversize box E7)
  - Alumni Association (prints) (Box I-1)
  - Apartment drawing by Milton Kemnitz (Box I-1)
  - Bands
    - Marching, n.d. 1998 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Marching and Jazz undated (prints) (Box I-1)
  - Campus Buildings
    - Central Campus (prints) (Box I-1)
    - Medical Campus (negatives and prints), 2 folders (Box I-1)
    - Michigan Stadium 1991, 1998 (prints and slides) (Box I-1)
    - Miscellaneous (negatives) (Box I-1)
    - Miscellaneous 1988, 1995-1998 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Miscellaneous and Unidentified (includes Flint and Dearborn Campuses, etc.) (prints) (Box I-1)
    - North Campus (prints) (Box I-1)
    - North Campus Construction
      - May 1953-May 1955 (negatives) (Box I-1)
      - June 1955-1956, undated (negatives) (Box I-1)
      - undated (prints) (Box I-1)
    - South Campus (prints) (Box I-1)
    - Statues, fixtures, landscaping, etc. (prints) (Box I-1)
  - Campus Events
    - Miscellaneous (negatives) (Box I-1)
    - Miscellaneous 1960s-1990s (prints and 1 slide) (Box I-1)
    - Graduation
      - 1988, 1993 (slides) (Box I-1)
      - 1991 (prints) (Box I-1)
  - Campus Scenes
    - Art Fair
      - undated (prints) (Box I-1)
      - 1995 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Campus: General (prints) (Box I-1)
    - Classrooms/Labs 1995-1996 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Football Games 1995-1996, 1998 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Miscellaneous (negatives, slides, contact sheets) (Box I-1)
    - Miscellaneous 1970, 1973, 1994-1998 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Students/Student Life (prints) (Box I-1)
  - Community/Service Projects (prints) (Box I-1)
  - Departments
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
      - undated (prints) (Box I-1)
      - December 1997 (slides) (Box I-1)
    - Art (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Automotive Engineering (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Business Administration (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Dental School (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Education, School of (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Engineering (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Law School (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Medical School: Historical, [1890s] (negatives) (Box I-2)
    - Music, School of 1982 (negatives) (Box I-2)
    - Pharmacy, College of (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Physics (prints) (Box I-2)
    - Psychology December 1997 (slides) (Box I-2)
  - Engineering Summer Conference at Chrysler 1968 (negatives and contact sheets), 2 folders (Box I-2)
  - Faculty and Staff
    - Negatives (Box I-2)
    - Prints, arranged alphabetically, 3 folders
      - Aigler, Ralph-Faculty Representative (Box I-2)
      - Alfred, Richard L. (Box I-2)
      - Allan, J. David (Box I-2)
      - Amidei, Dante (Box I-2)
      - Arnheim, Rudolf (Box I-2)
      - Atreya, Arvind 1994 (Box I-2)
      - Bailey, Rich (Box I-2)
      - Barnes, Burton (Box I-2)
      - Barritt, Loren (Box I-2)
      - Bates, Percy-Faculty Representative (Box I-2)
      - Beaver, Frank (Box I-2)
      - Bole, Giles (Box I-2)
      - Boehm, Susan (Box I-2)
      - Brei, Diann Erbschloe-MEAM 1994 (Box I-2)
      - Brown, Paul (Box I-2)
      - Brusati, Celeste (Box I-2)
      - Cantor, Nancy-Provost (Box I-2)
      - Carson, Benjamin (Box I-2)
      - Chamberlain, Jeffrey S., Ph.D.-Assistant Professor of Human Genetics (Box I-2)
      - Chamberlin, John R. (Box I-2)
      - Chard, Lynn P.-Director, Institute of Continuing Legal Education 1993 (Box I-2)
      - Checkoway, Barry (Box I-2)
      - Cohen, Carl 1992 (Box I-2)
      - Cooper, Kevin D., M.D.-Immunodermatology Unit (Box I-2)
      - Correa, Charles (Box I-2)
      - Cornell, Richard (Box I-2)
      - Cosovich, Jon (Box I-2)
      - Crary, Joan (Box I-2)
      - D'Arms, John H. (Box I-2)
      - Duderstadt, James-President (slides) (Box I-2)
      - Fader, Lester, and Reginald Malcolmson-Architecture (Box I-2)
      - Feuerwerker, Yi-Tsi Mei (Box I-2)
      - Fisk, L.A.-AOSS 1993 (Box I-2)
      - Fleming, President and Mrs. with members of Mortarboard 1976 (Box I-2)
      - Fricke, ? (Box I-2)
      - Gelderloos, Orin (Box I-2)
      - Gilligan, Caral (Box I-2)
      - Goebel, Paul (Box I-2)
      - Gray, Bob-Public Health (Box I-2)
      - Green, ? (Box I-2)
      - Hanss, Theodore A., Jr.-Director of CITI (Box I-2)
      - Hart, Stuart-Business Administration (Box I-2)
      - Hays, Paul B.-AOSS 1991 (Box I-2)
      - Hinshaw, Ada Sue (Box I-2)
      - Hutchcroft, C. Robert-School of Education (Box I-2)
      - Johnson, Harold 1994 (Box I-2)
      - Johnson, Lemuel A.,-English (Box I-2)
      - Johnson, Susan (Box I-2)
      - Jones, Beverly (Box I-2)
      - Jones, Clinton B. (Box I-2)
      - Jones, Wayne-MSE 1995 (Box I-2)
      - Kamisar, Yale (Box I-2)
      - Kammash, Terry (Box I-2)
      - Kennedy, Richard (Box I-2)
      - Kessler, Ronald C., and Amanda Sonnega-Sociology, Institute for Social Research (Box I-2)
      - Koopman, James S.-Public Health (Box I-2)
      - Lehman (Box I-2)
      - Libin, Lawrence (Box I-2)
      - Machen, J. Bernard (Box I-2)
      - Malcolmson, Reginald (see Fader, Lester) (Box I-2)
      - Malm, William P. 1980 (Box I-2)
      - Markus, Hazel (Box I-2)
      - Martin, James (Box I-2)
      - Matthews, Rowena 1994 (Box I-2)
      - McNamara, J.A. (Box I-2)
      - McClain, Jackie-Executive Director, Human Resources and Affirmative Action (Box I-2)
      - McGowan, Rebecca-Democratic Candidate for University of Michigan Board of Regents 1992 (Box I-2)
      - Meyerhoff, Mark (Box I-2)
      - Miller, Jim-Engineering 1990 (Box I-2)
      - Miller, Josef (Box I-2)
      - Monts, Lester P.-vice Provost for Academic and Multicultural Affairs (Box I-2)
      - Nair, Madhavan (Box I-2)
      - Neal, Homer-Vice President for Research (Box I-2)
      - Newman, Sara 1995 (Box I-2)
      - Ortega, Robert-Social Work (Box I-2)
      - Osborn, June-Public Health (Box I-2)
      - Paul, Ara-Dean, Pharmacy (Box I-2)
      - Pennington, Parker (Box I-2)
      - Peterson, Robert-Alumni Center (Box I-2)
      - Plant, Marcus-Faculty Representative (Box I-2)
      - Power, Philip H.-Regent (Box I-2)
      - Preston, Stephen (Box I-2)
      - Radin, Norman (Box I-2)
      - Reznicek, Tony (Box I-2)
      - Rice, Werner G. (Box I-2)
      - Riggs, Don (Box I-2)
      - Rockwell, Richard-Institute for Social Research (Box I-2)
      - Royce, Toni-U-M Hospital 1968 (Box I-2)
      - Schmoll, Beverly 1995 (Box I-2)
      - Schoem, David (Box I-2)
      - Shurin, H.-Psychology (Box I-2)
      - Shields, Dennis 1991 (Box I-2)
      - Smith, B. Holly-Anthropology 1987 (Box I-2)
      - Sonnega, Amanda (see Kessler, Ronald C.) (Box I-2)
      - Sousounis, Peter-AOSS 1992 (Box I-2)
      - Voss, Burton (Box I-2)
      - Wagaw, ? (Box I-2)
      - Walker, James C.G. 1995 (Box I-2)
      - Weaver, M. (Box I-2)
      - Wenful, Herbert (Box I-2)
      - Wilbanks, Cynthia (Box I-2)
      - Williams, Frank (Box I-2)
      - Wooley, Trevor (Box I-2)
      - Yates, Frank (Box I-2)
  - Friars 1970 (negatives) (Box I-2)
  - Gates, Max (photographer?) (negatives), 2 folders (Box I-2)
  - Glee Club Tour: Flint December 1968 (negatives and contact sheets), 2 folders (Box I-2)
  - Miscellaneous (prints and negatives) (Box I-2)
  - Railroad: views of train owned by U-M 1948 (negatives) (Box I-2)
  - Regents Forum Sponsored by Communication on Issue of Classified Research 1971(negatives) (Box I-2)
  - Research: Great Lakes (negatives) (Box I-2)
  - Sports
    - Negatives (Box I-2)
    - Prints, arranged alphabetically, 3 folders
      - Aerobics (Box I-2)
      - Baseball (Box I-2)
      - Basketball, Men's (Box I-2)
      - Basketball, Women's (Box I-2)
      - Children's Recreation (Box I-2)
      - Cross Country (Box I-2)
      - Football (Box I-2)
      - Golf, Women's (Box I-2)
      - Gymnastics, Men's (Box I-2)
      - Gymnastics, Women's (Box I-2)
      - Hockey (Box I-2)
      - Softball (Box I-2)
      - Synchronized Swimming (Box I-2)
      - Tennis, Men's (Box I-2)
      - Tennis, Women's (Box I-2)
      - Weight Training (Box I-2)
    - Slides
      - Basketball 1996-1997 (Box I-2)
      - Cheerleading 1997-1998 (Box I-2)
      - Field Hockey 1995-1996 (Box I-2)
      - Football 1996 (Box I-2)
  - Student Projects (prints) (Box I-2)
  - Unidentified (negatives) (Box I-2)
- Series J (University Record Photographic Prints) 1987-1998
  Series J - University Record Photos (6 linear feet, 1987-1998) is comprised of prints that were used in the University Record the faculty and staff newspaper with broad coverage of campus events. It spans 11 years, starting with a general folder for 1987, and ending in April 1998. It covers volume number 42 through volume number 53 of the University Record. It is broken down into two sub-series: Prints and Prints Not Used. The series of prints is organized in chronological order by the date that each edition of the University Record was published. The prints not used are organized chronologically by when the prints were taken and cover the years 1978-1983, 1991-1996, or 1997-1998. The contents of the prints series and prints not used series cover a wide array of campus images, ranging from faculty and staff to visiting speakers, buildings and student events. The collection provides a good visual overview of the university from the decade between 1988-1998.
  - 1987 (Box J1)
  - March 17, 1988 (Box J1)
  - May 9, 1988 (Box J1)
  - May 23, 1988 (Box J1)
  - June 6, 1988 (Box J1)
  - June 20, 1988 (Box J1)
  - June 5, 1988 (Box J1)
  - July 18, 1988 (Box J1)
  - August 1, 1988 (Box J1)
  - August 22, 1988 (Box J1)
  - September 6, 1988 (Box J1)
  - September 12, 1988 (Box J1)
  - September 19, 1988 (Box J1)
  - September 25, 1988 (Box J1)
  - October 3, 1988 (Box J1)
  - October 10, 1988 (Box J1)
  - October 17, 1988 (Box J1)
  - October 24, 1988 (Box J1)
  - October 31, 1988 (Box J1)
  - November 7, 1988 (Box J1)
  - November 14, 1988 (Box J1)
  - November 21, 1988 (Box J1)
  - December 5, 1988 (Box J1)
  - December 12, 1988 (Information Tech Supplement) (Box J1)
  - December 19, 1988 (Box J1)
  - January 16, 1989 (Box J1)
  - January 23, 1989 (Box J1)
  - January 30, 1989 (Box J1)
  - February 6, 1989 (Box J1)
  - February 13, 1989 (Box J1)
  - February 20, 1989 (Box J1)
  - February 28, 1989 (Box J1)
  - March 6, 1989 (Box J1)
  - March 13, 1989 (Box J1)
  - March 20, 1989 (Box J1)
  - March 27, 1989 (Box J1)
  - April 3, 1989 (Box J1)
  - April 10, 1989 (Box J1)
  - April 17, 1989 (Box J1)
  - April 24, 1989 (Box J1)
  - May 8, 1989 (Box J1)
  - May 22, 1989 (Box J1)
  - June 5, 1989 (Box J1)